ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND PRODUCTS
ARE FICTIONAL AND DRAMATIZED
AND DO NOT REFLECT REALITY
Hello.
Distinguished guests,
welcome to Boudoir's 2024 SS collection.
Over here, please!
Look over here, please!
Shin So-ui seems to know her.
Wow. It's snowing!
Hey, look at that!
Truth,
like light,
blinds us.
Falsehood, on the other hand,
is like a beautiful sunset
that enhances everything.
That is, until you get caught.
Come on, hurry.
- Is it here?
- I think it's there.
Is that the line?
What time is it?
Hey, do you have one more hand warmer?
We need more hand warmers.
Of course I was camping outside
Apgujeong Hyundai and Apgujeong Galleria.
They're holding out on me
because they recognize me.
They're making such a fuss,
and they're not even BKC.
Hey.
I'll be at the Lotte Main Store.
The silver Classic Medium drop
hit the chats.
Okay.
I was sitting there, and…
Oh, I can't bear to look.
Good morning.
The person was dead,
her face half mangled…
Good morning.
We've been searching for hours,
but are yet to find an ID or a cell phone.
What about prints?
No matches.
We found a bag here.
It seems she's been left here for days.
I guess there's no one in her life
to report her missing.
THE ART OF SARAH
JANE DOE
METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
We lifted partial prints
from the clasp of the bag.
They're not enough to identify her,
but enough for a comparison.
- Compared to the victim's?
- It's a match.
And some aren't.
Could they be the perpetrator's?
We can't rule it out.
But, you know… How shall I put this?
It feels like a show-off.
- Did you find something else?
- No.
I mean, this bag.
The color and leather choice is so unique.
I bet there are only a few
with this combo in the world.
Bags like these
have serial numbers.
Here.
- Sir?
- Yes.
- Police.
- Sorry?
Sir, we kindly ask that you wait outside.
Would it be possible…
to find out who purchased
this particular product?
The severity of the facial depression
suggests a vicious crime of passion.
The victim's face was repeatedly struck
until the nose and gums caved in.
Bam…
But that was not the cause of death.
Exposure was.
She slowly froze to death.
She froze to death
right in Cheongdam-dong?
We had a record-breaking cold snap.
SPLENDID MELANCHOLY
"Splendid melancholy."
JANE DOE?
The fact that there are barely any traces
means this was no ordinary person.
The perpetrator?
Do you know how much this costs?
If the perpetrator left this bag behind
like it was nothing,
that means they're either insane
or insanely rich.
Who are you?
Hello, sir.
I'm Hyeon Jae-hyeon, assigned
to Violent Crimes Team One as of today.
Whose bag is it?
The owner of the purple bag
is Jeong Yeo-jin,
CEO of the cosmetic brand Nox.
Apparently, she gave the bag to a friend.
Now, that's an uncanny coincidence.
Well, we should investigate further,
but it looks like
we have the victim's identity.
All right. Good work.
Are you meeting someone about the case?
Should I come along?
Your desk.
Your job.
Yes, this is Violent Crimes Team One.
Would you take a look here too?
Oh my God.
It's her. It's Sarah.
We can stop if this is too hard for you.
I'd…
I'd like to have a moment alone.
Very well. I'll give you five minutes.
MORGUE
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
She gave the bag to Sarah Kim,
the regional head of this company.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You two must have been very close.
Well, I gave her that bag.
That says it all, doesn't it?
I'd like to hear more details.
It all began with the Birkin bag.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Are you looking for
anything in particular?
I thought it'd be Epsom,
but it's Clemence leather.
I can try it on, right?
Please be careful with the bag.
I'm sorry,
but photography isn't allowed
inside the store.
Would you kindly delete the photos?
May I store that for you?
No. It's fine.
Ma'am.
Please observe only--
I'll take everything I've touched so far.
Sorry?
I said I'll buy everything
I've touched so far.
You remember them all, right?
Let me help you sign up
for membership first.
May I have your name, please?
Sarah Kim.
You must have spent time abroad.
And your address?
Just fill in the rest
with your information.
Sorry?
Of course.
Your membership is all set.
We can proceed to your payment.
May I have your credit card and ID?
But I'm paying in cash.
Here is one million won.
That makes ten million in total.
Here is five million.
That was the moment Sarah became
someone I could never forget.
She was odd, yet I was oddly drawn to her.
I've been waiting for half a year.
I figured you might be waiting,
so I contacted you
the moment the tracking number came out.
Could I try this bag on?
I'm sorry.
That bag is a special-order item.
Is it, by any chance,
for Sarah Kim?
All I knew was her name,
but I instinctively knew
she was someone extraordinary.
- Because everyone noticed Sarah.
- Sarah Kim?
Yes, Sarah Kim.
She's Boudoir's Head of Asia Operations
and the sponsor of my latest movie.
Boudoir?
First time hearing it, right?
It's a high-end brand that's served
European royalty for 100 years.
Apparently, it only sells to the top 0.1%.
Let me see.
They're launching in Korea too.
I might have heard of it.
So she's their regional head.
Goodness, why are portions here so small?
Tell me about it.
We don't have great seats either.
Someone's all dressed up today.
Who are you trying to impress?
Don't tell me it's an ex.
An ex? I would've been way past that.
No, this one's
far more shameless and nasty.
You must be in the middle
of a VIP gathering.
- Hello, Chairwoman.
- Who were you again?
I send you our products every year,
but they don't seem
to be reaching you successfully.
The CEO of Nox.
Drugstore cosmetics.
I see.
You don't deal with local brands,
Chairwoman.
So, what brings you by?
Since we ran into each other,
I wanted to ask about the reason
you rejected my membership application.
The reason?
The purpose of our gathering
is to spend time with people
who see, feel, and enjoy the same things.
In that sense, I concluded
that we don't necessarily align.
We don't "align"?
Is that all it was?
Saying "Is that all it was?"
would make your life too miserable.
"That" is the reason
you're sitting by the restroom
and I'm sitting up here.
I see you don't understand,
so let me use how we approach food
as an example.
Class often shows
in whether one prioritizes
quantity, quality, or presentation.
I prioritize presentation.
How about you?
Quantity or quality?
We've only just met.
Why do you assume you know me?
I think I do know you.
Fine. Let's take how one views
luxury goods as an example.
Do you prioritize the price, the logo,
or the rarity?
Shall I take a guess?
You value all three.
Whatever it is,
you want to appear to have it all.
I believe they call that desperation.
- Did you see her bag?
- I'm so embarrassed for her.
- Seriously.
- What on earth?
- Oh no!
- My God. Excuse me.
- My precious bag!
- Hold on.
It's fine. I'll do it.
I'm so sorry.
Stop that.
I'm sorry.
I said stop!
My bag!
I'm very sorry.
This is all my fault.
How can I make this up to you?
We're both at fault. So just go.
Then how about we do this?
What are you doing?
I won't make empty promises
about getting you the same bag,
and you're refusing compensation.
And I think this color goes better
with your outfit.
So how about a fair trade?
If you know the value of that bag,
I'm sure you know
the value of this one too.
You're the CEO of Nox, right?
I'm a fan of this lipstick too.
Ms. Jeong. Care to go for round two?
Who could possibly turn down
an offer like that?
- One, two…
Sarah was always making me
offers I couldn't refuse.
She was always doing that.
Whipped cream cake with soju?
Mismatches sometimes make
the perfect combination.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I took my anger out on the wrong person.
Is the spot where I hit you okay?
Actually, I used to do shot put.
Ms. Jeong.
You were practically
an attempted murderer.
Oh, that pile of cash.
- That was you, right?
- Did you see me?
Oh God, that's so embarrassing.
I had just arrived in Korea,
so I hadn't even washed up properly.
I thought you were a total nightmare.
Please forget that.
Something that impactful?
No, that's not possible.
Come on. Nothing's impossible.
I even befriended an attempted murderer.
I can think of plenty.
Since you work in the luxury industry,
you must've seen plenty like me.
People splashing their cash
to lose the "new money" tag.
They say flaunting
is a sign of insecurity.
Does it show a lot?
What about me?
Can you tell?
Hey. You and I are different.
You're a Korean American
who went to Oxford.
You're as elite as they come,
so don't try to relate.
They say true wealth shows
in your air miles, not your bank balance.
They're not wrong.
There's more than meets the eye.
I wish it would snow.
Like heavy flurries.
But it's the middle of summer.
That would be impossible.
Who knows?
It just hasn't happened yet.
Sarah was perfectly perfect that day.
That day, I realized
I had endured over 40 years of loneliness
just to meet Sarah.
It's not who you are that matters
but who you appear to be.
- That's how we became friends.
- Presence and nuance.
Those beneath me envied me for what I had,
and those above me looked down on me
for what I lacked.
Sarah was the only one…
This is nice.
…who brought me the things I desired.
That's a Yoo Yeong piece. Gonna buy it?
SENSES BEYOND THE CANVAS
YOO YEONG
The rights, not the piece.
It'd be great
as the launch gift box design.
You don't think others have made offers?
Dozens have tried and failed.
That makes me like it more.
They say you only ever get two answers
from Yoo Yeong.
Either "call rejected" or "email unread."
She's simply impossible to reach.
I guess you pay attention
to what people who have failed say,
but not to what I say.
I told you.
It just hasn't happened yet.
If you want to know the value of someone,
focus on what they don't have,
not what they have.
The Sarah I know
didn't leave lipstick smudges on cups,
didn't have space
in the backseat of her car,
and acted without hesitation.
ARTIST YOO YEONG
Not gonna answer?
I want her to get more desperate.
Wow.
How did you coax her?
There are three things
artists absolutely can't bear.
One, "I am ordinary."
Two, "I am ordinary."
And three,
"I am ordinary."
So you flattered her as being unique.
I called her ordinary.
Now she's dying to prove me wrong.
What's with all the luggage back there?
I want to move hotels.
I think the housekeeper
is going through my stuff.
Why don't you come to my house instead?
The second floor is empty.
Really?
Sounds good.
Yay!
Are you sure you're 38?
You look like a twenty-something.
You can buy anything with money.
Even youth.
I wish it would snow.
But it's the middle of summer.
That would be impossible.
I told you.
It just hasn't happened yet.
It was the most beautiful fake
I had ever laid eyes on.
Is that the bag you traded with Sarah Kim?
Why do you think the suspect
left the Birkin bag at the scene?
If not for that, identifying the victim
might have been impossible.
Maybe it's a ploy to frame me
as the murderer.
There is a reason
behind every clue at a scene.
I am looking for those reasons,
not the clues.
Does anything come to mind?
I'm not sure.
Even as friends,
I am sure things were not always good.
At this age,
being able to make a new friend
is an incredibly rare thing.
It's far more challenging
than owning a Birkin,
and far harder
than pulling one off.
Oh my!
It made me think of you.
Hey, how do I look?
Does it suit me?
- Here, let me.
- Yeah?
Like this. Here.
- Try walking around with it.
- Okay.
I don't suppose Boudoir
is planning on doing ready-to-wear?
It'd be nice to have matching outfit sets.
We have our sights on something bigger.
I plan to build Hotel Boudoir,
filled with Boudoir items.
From the furniture and wallpaper
to the lighting, towels, dishes,
and even the fragrance.
That means you would need amenities too.
I'd imagine so.
What if our brands joined forces?
Anything is possible.
I don't know.
Don't you think Boudoir and Nox
have different objectives?
After she said that,
she went around
having meals with Choi Chae-u.
How about making
a strategic investment in Boudoir?
We can discuss it
after reviewing the company.
What if we lose our chance
by sticking to procedure?
More importantly,
I don't think
the two brands necessarily align.
We've been in talks
about investment with a place.
Do we need to take a risk?
"Align"?
By that, are you taking a shot at Boudoir
or at Nox?
I'm saying let's leverage Boudoir's name,
since I'm sick of hearing crap like this.
Come on, people.
Let's level up already.
Yeo-jin.
Yes?
I think we're dreaming the same dream.
- How much should I invest?
- How much can you do?
Ten billion won.
Add five billion to that.
Okay.
The gray hair shampoo
will soon be approved by the FDS,
so invest as much as you can.
Weren't you in talks
to invest in this company?
- Something about expanding your bath line?
- Well…
I think the shampoo and Nox
have different objectives.
What's going on?
You heard a good investment tip somewhere,
didn't you?
Come on, do share.
Don't keep it all to yourself.
Seriously.
I know.
Boudoir. I invested in Boudoir.
- Oh, Sarah Kim's brand?
- Yes.
Isn't that a bit hasty?
Frankly, I hadn't heard
of the brand until recently.
That's understandable.
After all,
Boudoir only sells to the top 0.1%.
Honestly.
Unbelievable.
It wasn't long
until they came to regret it dearly.
FLAGSHIP STORE OPENS IN ASIA
EUROPEAN LUXURY BRAND BOUDOIR
Boudoir was a hit.
It was a huge success.
It was at the center of attention
as soon as it arrived.
The people who make the world go around
flocked to it like moths to a flame.
BOUDOIR IS A PIECE OF ART, NOT A BAG
IT'S A EUROPEAN ROYALTY BRAND
A CLASS OF ITS OWN
BOUDOIR IS SOLD OUT AGAIN?
BOUDOIR STORE ROCKS!
DEPOSIT ALERT
Wait. 1.5 billion?
I received 1.5 billion won in dividends
for the first month.
At that rate, it was like raking in money
while sitting down.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
That day marked the end of one style
and the rise of a new trend.
Because Boudoir had launched
its new collection.
And that was the last day I saw Sarah.
Sarah seemed like she could leave
at the drop of a hat.
She never unpacked her suitcase
in the entire time
she was staying at my house.
That hurt me back then.
If I had
reported Sarah missing right away,
would things have turned out differently?
Would you send me a photo of her?
I should know what the victim looks like.
Sadly, I don't have any.
She never liked having her picture taken.
I see.
Thank you for your time.
- Isn't that odd?
- What?
She put the Birkin on the floor.
The bag even has history
with her late friend.
Either the bag's fake
or the friendship is. Or both.
- Maybe that's a stretch.
- One more thing.
One moment.
She never loses her composure
throughout the interview.
Everything's too perfect.
Both Jeong Yeo-jin
and the Sarah Kim she speaks of.
- Am I the only one who finds this odd?
- I agree.
It is odd. I mean, you are, sir.
You're saying there's something wrong
because nothing's wrong.
The fact is, she looks like a woman
dazed by the loss of a friend.
That's a bias, not a fact.
Well, just because you're not hungry,
you think we won't be either.
That is a bias.
Seriously, aren't you going to eat?
Then do you mind if we do?
Let's go.
- We'll be back.
- See you later.
Come on.
NAME: JEONG YEO-JIN
INVESTIGATION SUBJECT SEARCH
JEONG YEO-JIN
ROBBERY-LINKED ASSAULT
SUMMONS TO APPEAR
FINANCIAL CRIMES INVESTIGATION UNIT
Sir, hold on!
Verify that the murder victim, Sarah Kim,
is a US citizen with Foreign Affairs.
Sir?
FINANCIAL CRIMES INVESTIGATION UNIT
To what do I owe the dishonor?
I need some information.
My case and yours
have something in common.
Jeong Yeo-jin.
Oh, that case.
We arrested a suspect
for kidnapping, assault, and extortion.
But it turned out someone had hired them.
And that was Jeong Yeo-jin.
The suspect said Jeong demanded
that Kim repay the funds she invested,
but Kim didn't comply.
A whopping 15 billion won in total.
Not even best friends
can withstand the test of money.
And this part is still confidential,
but it seems that Jeong
siphoned off company funds to invest.
It's been months!
I haven't received a dime
since the first month.
See, this is why I said
I didn't want to work with you.
You're so desperate and impatient
about every little thing.
You're wound so tight
that you still seem like a tacky commoner,
despite being a CEO.
I wouldn't do this if it were my money!
The investment funds came
from misappropriated company money.
What?
I'm in real trouble.
If there's an audit--
Why the hell did you do that?
I told you to do only what you're told!
Why are you angry?
You're the one not paying up!
Yeo-jin.
If you get caught, you're done for.
I'm concerned for you, see?
Yeo-jin.
Don't say a word about this to anyone.
Wow.
How did you get this?
Why?
Just a moment.
Now,
can you tell which one's the fake?
No, I can't.
Which is why you were fooled.
Here, take a look.
Closer.
It's a little too perfect, isn't it?
A highly evolved counterfeit
surpasses the authentic.
Because the real thing
doesn't aim for perfection.
You're saying it's perfect,
so it's a fake?
Yes. 100%.
Wow. I've never seen
anything like this before.
So, would you like me
to take it off your hands?
How much is it worth, then?
Five million won?
Five and a half?
The victim was no ordinary person either.
Or maybe she has some serious pull.
I even got pressure from higher up
to make this case a priority.
Well, she is the regional head of Boudoir.
"The regional head"?
No, the victim was a salesperson.
A salesperson?
Name, Woo Hyo-eun. Age, 30.
They must've mixed something up.
They kidnapped the salesperson
instead of Sarah Kim.
- Here.
- Her name is Woo Hyo-eun?
DRIVER'S LICENSE
WOO HYO-EUN
Let's run a fingerprint search.
- Hey, where's our fingerprinting kit?
- Yes?
Oh, I understand.
Have a good day.
- Hey, Ji-hun.
- Yes?
Start the report first.
Yes, ma'am.
She has a cast on her left leg
and bruises on her face.
Just make it through a week.
Excuse me.
I don't have a handkerchief.
Do you know me?
I'm sure every person passing through
a police station has a story.
Just call it philanthropy.
A navy tie will go better with that suit
than this.
You got it wrong.
The crutch should be on the other side.
Hey, Park Mu-gyeong!
The suspect, Min Byeong-kwan,
said he'd give your team intel on Boudoir.
Did you look into it?
The Boudoir bags
they snatched as collateral…
Well, if what he claims is true,
they were all counterfeit.
Who received the intel about Boudoir?
I did.
Foreign Affairs just replied
saying they can't verify the identity.
What?
There is no Sarah Kim.
No one matches that name,
age, birthplace, or education.
JANE DOE
Subtitle translation by: Yung Un Choi